innity.com 2019-12-24

# Privacy Policy | Innity - Right Audience, Real Engagement

##### This privacy policy applies to all of the products and services offered by INNITY or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies.

### Introduction

Innity’s Advenue is a digital advertising technology platform that manages the online display campaigns for advertisers. It is designed to compose, deliver and optimize millions of highly relevant ad experiences across search, display and social media from a single platform. Advenue’s technological platform does not use any personally identifiable information for these or any other purpose.

This Privacy Policy describes Innity’s methods and policies with transparency on how we use and process data when providing Advenue service. It also defines how Advenue’s clients and third-party affiliates using Advenue’s services, governs their own data while Advenue only has limited rights to utilize such data for the purpose of providing the Service on behalf of their clients and third-party affiliates.

Innity advocates online privacy and has ensured compliance with the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), to effectively generate a secured and safe advertising environment for all parties and to promote a strong marketplace for more effective and targeted advertising.

### How Advenue Works

Advenue provides tools for advertisers to buy advertising space across digital channels such as websites and mobile applications. Likewise, it also enables publishers of websites and mobile applications to offer and sell their advertising space.

Advenue also provides tools to manage, buy and sell data that can be utilized for targeted advertising and delivery of advertising content to a specific website or mobile application.

Advenue also employs tools to measure Ad effectiveness, engagement and audience reach as well as to implement anti-fraud and anti-malware activities.

### Data Collection and Usage

Data or information that is collected through our Advenue platform will only be used by Innity with legal responsibility and respect to privacy regulation, whereby Innity acts as a Data Controller. Information collected are processed by Innity on behalf of its clients and Innity adheres to the instructions of its clients in duration of processing their data.

Generally, we only collect anonymous, non-Personal Identifiable Information, such as browser type, operating system, IP address and response or feedback to an Ad.

We Do Not Collect and Use:

  * Personal Identifiable Information (PII).

  * Your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, ID number, credit card information, or anything else that can personally identify you.

  * Sensitive Consumer Information, such as insurance plan numbers, financial account numbers, or information about medical conditions.

We only use the non-Personal Identifiable Information via cookies for the purpose of targeting and measuring the effectiveness of Ads on behalf of Innity's advertisers and to identify the audience most likely to respond to an advertisement. This information also helps Innity ensure that you don't repeatedly see the same ad. We may also use non-PII data from third parties.

In order to operate Advenue, Innity uses two technologies to collect information:

### Cookies

Cookies are small text files that web sites place in your browser when you visit them or see an Ad. When you return to the site or view another Ad, a site can access these cookie files. Sites can then determine how often you've visited a site or seen an Ad. Cookies cannot be used to access any other data on your computer.

### Pixel Tags

Pixel tags are small images on a web page or other document. Pixel tags allow the operator of the web page or other document, or a third party who serves the pixel tag, to set, read, and modify cookies.

### Consent to Collect and Use Your Data

In compliance with GDPR, Innity will conform to the policies of the IAB Europe Transparency and Consent Framework as a registered vendor on IAB Europe’s Global Vendor List. Consent will be processed before collecting and using your data. You will have control to fully opt in or opt out or to allow partial data for processing to facilitate Advenue’s operations. We will respect and comply with the indications that are disseminated to us according to the Framework.

Consent will be processed for:

  1. **Personalisation**

The collection and processing of information about your use of this service to subsequently personalise advertising and/or content for you in other contexts, such as on other websites or apps, over time. Typically, the content of the site or app is used to make inferences about your interests, which inform future selection of advertising and/or content. 

  2. **Information Storage and Access**

The storage of information, or access to information that is already stored, on your device such as advertising identifiers, device identifiers, cookies, and similar technologies. 

  3. **Ad Selection, Delivery, Reporting**

The collection of information, and combination with previously collected information, to select and deliver advertisements for you, and to measure the delivery and effectiveness of such advertisements. 

This includes using previously collected information about your interests to select Ads, processing data about what advertisements were shown, how often they were shown, when and where they were shown, and whether you took any action related to the advertisement, including for example, clicking an Ad or making a purchase. 

*This does not include personalisation, which is the collection and processing of information about your use of this service to subsequently personalise advertising and/or content for you in other contexts, such as websites or apps, over time. 

  4. **Content Selection, Delivery, Reporting**

The collection of information, and combination with previously collected information, to select and deliver content for you, and to measure the delivery and effectiveness of such content. This includes using previously collected information about your interests to select content, processing data about what content was shown, how often or how long it was shown, when and where it was shown, and whether you took any action related to the content, including for example clicking on content. 

*This does not include personalisation, which is the collection and processing of information about your use of this service to subsequently personalise content and/or advertising for you in other contexts, such as websites or apps, over time. 

  5. **Measurement**

The collection of information about your use of the content, and combination with previously collected information, used to measure, understand, and report on your usage of the service. 

*This does not include personalisation, the collection of information about your use of this service to subsequently personalise content and/or advertising for you in other contexts, i.e. on other service, such as websites or apps, over time. 

### Right to Access Your Data

All Innity and Advenue users have the right to access their data and the right to obtain a copy of their personal data as well as other supplementary information. You are entitled to obtain the following information from us:

  * a copy of your personal data

  * confirmation that we are processing your personal data

  * other supplementary information

Upon your request, all detailed information of your existing data including the various ways we are using your information, will be sent to you electronically.

### Right to Data Portability

After you have received your data from us, Innity and Advenue are no longer responsible for the data handed over to you. You may exercise your right of data portability to transmit those data to another controller, where technically feasible.

### Right to Data Deletion

All Innity and Advenue users have the right to have their personal data erased or deleted by sending us a request to delete the information collected by Innity, Advenue or any of our affiliates. You also have the right to personal data erasure or deletion for:

  * data that is no longer necessary for the purpose which was originally collected or processed for

  * when you withdraw the consent previously given for holding the data

  * when you withdraw the consent to the processing of data for legitimate interests or marketing purposes

  * when you are required to comply with legal obligation

  * data that is unintentionally distributed to or accessed by minors

### Data Security, Storage and Retention

Implementation of appropriate methodological security measures are in place to safeguard the personal information that is voluntarily submitted to us via our website or collected through interactions with our services. However, as no system is 100% secure, we make no guarantees on the safety or security of any data transmitted to or from our site or through our services.

The data collected through browser-level measurement is typically maintained for up to 12 months. Such data may be aggregated and used for analytical purposes indefinitely. Additionally, in certain circumstances, for instance when a specific site has asked for detailed reporting, selected anonymous records relating to that specific site may be maintained indefinitely.

### Information Relating to Children

Our products and services are not designed nor intended for anyone aged below 13 years. We do not intentionally collect information from anyone under the age of 13. However, upon notification that such information from a child has been transmitted to us, we will administer all reasonable efforts to locate and delete that information from our records.

### Disclosures

Some of our web site partners may place their own cookies on your Internet browser outside of our service; however, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

We retain the right to:

  * Transfer all data compiled or owned by us, in the event that another company acquires all or most of our assets. In such event, all the data will continue to be governed by this policy.

  * Transmit or share our data with third-party service providers (e.g., data storage and processing facilities) in order for those service providers to perform business functions for us or on our behalf.

  * Share, in an aggregated format, the non-Personally Identifiable Information we collect to do business with related third parties, such as our advertising clients.

  * Disclose your information to third parties when we reasonably believe we are obligated to do so by law, and in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual prohibited activities, including but not limited to, fraud and situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person.

### Data Collection for Our Corporate Site

Our web site (www.innity.com) is intended primarily to offer information about Innity and our services. Innity uses information from our web site log files to understand how visitors use our site and to recommend future site improvements. If you choose to submit personal information, we may use that information for general marketing purposes and to notify you regarding updates to our products and services. We do not sell, rent, share, or otherwise dispose of the personal information collected on www.innity.com to third parties. Once collected, we will store your information for a reasonable time for archiving purposes.

### Privacy Policy Updates

The terms of this privacy policy may be updated periodically and Innity reserves the right to change, modify, add or remove any portion of this policy without notice, therefore, we encourage you to visit this page from time to time to review any changes. Currently, we ensure that all privacy practices described here are up-to-date and in effect with our Advenue service.

### Concerns About This Policy

If you have any queries or comments concerning this policy, please contact us for more information.

E-mail: [privacy@innity.com](https://www.innity.com/mailto) Phone: +603 7880 5611 Address:C501&502,Kelana Square,17,Jalan SS7/26,Kelana Jaya,Petaling Jaya,Selangor,Malaysia.
